[Music]
this is a super late morning show with
the Lucas Bros K this is Keith yo it's
time for the weather man so let's just
go to Mook and see what it's
like hey
uh it's mad sunny out
today today we're honoring
real dads man man real dads that make
real choices man with honoring dead be
[Music]
father yeah so you know a lot of people
get mad at dead beat fathers for leaving
their kids I think it's great you know
what I mean it's awesome I think so we
brought one here it's all right we got a
real father just like our dad we got
Brian coming out here can we get Brian
let's get Brian can
[Applause]
we everything's going good for me I a
kiss I a kiss I do not
know I am yeah you made some tough
choices I made some tough choices man I
put people in the taxi pregnant I don't
know did you even get into the did you
even get into the taxi I don't like tax
all right see you even like know where
your son was born you know have any
idea at the hospital
okay gu Hospital definitely a hospital
right or taxi I don't know you weren't
there what were you doing I was on the
Block man I have to make money I mean I
got time to be sitting around cutting
umbilical cords and all this
that's beautiful see you can't be a dad
if you're such a good drug dealer I get
it man I mean you know priorities kind
of drug
deal
child baby I'm out live my life I'm we
got a prize for you for coming on our
show you know we're very grateful
actually got some tickets for you and
your sons to Disneyland bring on
Johnny
[Applause]
no actually man you got The Greatest
Prize man you got freedom freed that's
it's a beautiful thing thank you
Brian don't tell nobody I was
here on Monday we're going to have some
sunshine in the afternoon leading into
some clouds going to give it a 10 out of
10 for smoking weed Tuesday and
Wednesday is going to be some isolated
te- storms up in the Northwest I'm going
to give it a 10 out of 10 for smoking
weed Thursday a little more rain 10 out
of 10
Friday it's going to be back to the
sunshine guys but my parents are going
to be in town so I'm giving it a 9 out
of 10 for smoking weed but for all you
out there still going to be a 10 out of
[Music]
day
he